{
    "id": "a1fe5500db534420b9c4516ca9a8d2ac",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met a man ................................... had just returned from France.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will give you ...................................... you need.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The books .................................. you read are not worth reading.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Only he .................................... wears the shoes knows where it pinches.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The audience applauded Mary .................................... performance was spectacular.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "who's",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "John, ........................................ is always mischievous, was punished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Kochi, ........................................... has a natural harbor, can handle large ships.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my son of .......................................... I am very proud.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a writer ....................................... works are well-known.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who's",
                "whom",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the man .................................. house was burgled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "who's"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}